Dillon J. Ellis

Creative Solutions to Complex Problems

CONTACT

(770)-561-0377 www.dillonzellis.com dillonzellis@gmail.com Atlanta, GA

SKILLS

Expertise in various computer languages, frameworks, and databases focusing web design.

JavaScript, React, Node, Espress, Python, EJS, PHP, HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Bootstrap, MySQL, MongoDB, REST API, and Custom Wordpress.

Proficiency in Figma, Git, Github, NPM, Gulp, VSCode. Microsoft Office Word, PowerPoint, & Excel.

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Analytical Thinking
Problem Solving
Team Leadership
Organization
Problem Solving
Management Skills & Flexible
Strong Communication

REFERENCES

References available upon request.

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Hard-working, motivated individual. Well versed in various computer languages focusing web development with a background in empirical research studies from design to analyzing data. Possesses a Bachelor of Science, impeccable written and verbal communication skills, and excellent interpersonal skills.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

DZ Designs - Atlanta, GA

Owner, Design, and Development - Jan 2019 - Present

- · Acquired Clients.
- Conducted client meetings to determine client needs for development and budget.
- Design and Develop product.
- Set up maintenance packages including hosting, updates, revisions, backups, and security.

RLM Affairs - Gainesville, GA

Web Developer & Asst. Event Organizer - Mar 2017 - Present

- · Create and maintain company website.
- Regularly update website with new catering menu items and wedding packages.
- Tailored events according to the personal tastes and budgets of clients, managing and exceeding expectations.

RLM Florist - Gainesville, GA

Web Developer/IT & Asst Manager - Jan 2017 - Present

- Create, update, and maintain store ecommerce site with seasonal products and custom shipping and payment gateways.
- Address and resolve guest concerns, maintaining brand loyalty and increasing customer satisfaction ratings.

EDUCATION

University of North Georgia - Dalonegha, GA

Bachelor of Science in Psychological Sciences, Minor in CS - Dec 2017

University of North Georgia - Gainesville, GA

Associate of Arts in Psychological Sciences - May 2015

Relevant Coursework: Statistics, Research Methods, Web Programming, Software Engineering, and Databases.

Awards and Honors: Independent research in review of publication and SEPA reginonal Conference presentations.